ARJUNA ARRASYID

Full Stack Developer | +62 881 0246 77391 | arjunaarasyid62@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/arjuna-arrasyid-2256b2208/ | Bogor

OBJECTIVE

I am an experienced Full Stack Developer as well as Web Developer and Admin Office and Content Creator with 1 year experience. I have strong skills in web development and can use the latest technologies to build secure, reliable and efficient web applications. I have a high enthusiasm to overcome every problem and challenge in order to become a reliable and professional worker.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer | Full Stack Developer

Puncak Media Bogor | Aug 2023 - Jan 2024, Bogor

Build web-based application for Villa in Puncak Bogor with codeigniter 3 framework.

Admin

Puncak Media Bogor | Jan 2023 - Des 2023, Bogor

Serving customers, helping improve systems, entering customer data, and as a content creator.

Full Stack Developer

PT Madani Intersysdata | Aug 2021 - Jan 2023, Jakarta

Making a web-based corebanking prototype with the Spring Boot framework and mobile-based using Flutter framework

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

SMK Wikrama 1 Garut | Jul 2019 - Jul 2022, Garut

Enjoy learning new things especially about programming

SKILLS

HARD SKILLS

PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Java, Spring Boot, Java Script, Photoshop, Canva, Content Creator